我看到保时捷停在前门
I saw the Porsche parked out front.
你能把钥匙借给我一下吗
Can I get the keys?
我想带那个坏小子去兜个风
Thought I'd take that bad boy out for a spin.
等等  罗斯可以开你的保时捷
Wait a minute! You let Ross drive the Porsche
我问你时  你说只有你自己能开
and when I ask, you say you're the only one allowed to drive it.
他是我哥哥  而且他开车跟乌龟爬一样
He's my brother, plus he drives so slow
不会出事的
he could never hurt it.
那是辆车子  莫妮卡  又不是火箭飞船
It's a car, Monica, not a rocket ship.
罗斯
Whatever, Ross.
兜完风之后  帮我换一下刹车灯的灯泡
Just replace the bulbs in the brake lights after you're done.
我看到保时捷了  莫妮卡  看着很酷
Saw the Porsche out there, Mon. Looking good.
我什么时候能再开着它去兜风
When do I get to take that baby out again?
你让乔伊开保时捷
You let Joey drive it?
我从来没开过  一次都没有
I've never driven it, okay? Not once.
好吧  只有一次  好吧  我常开着出门
Okay, once. Okay, I drive it all the time.
我们的"你可以开它去兜风
Nice work, everybody. So much for the "you-can-drive-it
但别告诉瑞秋"计划宣告失败
but-don't-tell-Rachel" plan.
哇  我不敢相信你骗我
Wow, I can't believe you lied to me.
交给我来吧
I can fix this.
莫妮卡  瑞秋认为你满嘴只知道谈婚礼的事
Monica, Rachel thinks all you talk about is the wedding.
我不会让你开保时捷
Rachel, the reason why I won't let you drive the Porsche
因为你是个很差劲的司机
is because you're a terrible driver.
好了  这件事跟婚礼无关
There. That wasn't about the wedding.
如果你想开保时捷去兜风
Rach, if you want to go for a ride in the Porsche
我可以载你在街角转一下
I'll be glad to take you for a quick spin around the block.
你接下来几小时都没事吗
Yeah, you got a couple hours?
刚才真是痛快
Whew, that was a brisk ride.
-你开了车篷吧  -飞一般的感觉
- Take the top down, did you? - Only way to fly.
来嘛  罗斯  把钥匙给我
Come on, Ross. Give me the keys.
莫妮卡她冤枉我了
Monica does not know what she's talking about!
我是个很棒的司机
I'm an excellent driver.
你开车飞快  又不负责任
You're fast and irresponsible.
你的确是个差劲的司机
That adds up to a bad driver.
高中时  这几个特点让我成为啦啦队长
In high school, that added up to head cheerleader.
你看到那个女孩看我的眼神了吗
Did you see the look that girl just gave me?
她一定是看到了我开保时捷的模样
She must've seen me cruising in the bad boy.
-她在看你的鸟窝头  -什么
- She's checking out your beehive. - What?
-把梳子给我  -钥匙给我
- Give me a brush. - Give me the keys.
-不行  -那我就不给你梳子
- No way! - Well, no brush.
好吧  没关系
Fine. It doesn't matter.
如果我没记错
Because if I remember correctly,
洗手间地上有一把梳子
there's a comb on the floor of the bathroom.
这是我的赡养费
Alimony.
钱德勒  你爸还没寄回函给我们
Chandler, we still haven't gotten an RSVP from your dad.
对  或许那是因为我没寄喜贴给他
Oh, right. Maybe that's because I didn't send him an invitation.
他是你爸爸  他应该来参加我们的婚礼
Chandler, he's your father. He should be at our wedding.
我跟他根本不熟
I don't even know the man, okay?
我们关系很疏远  我好几年没跟他见过面了
We're not that close. I haven't seen him in years.
如果他知道我们没有邀请他呢
What are you gonna do when he finds out he wasn't even asked?
我们的生活圈不一样
He doesn't have to know! It's not like we run in the same circles.
我跟你们来往  而他...
I hang out with you guys and he...
他在拉斯维加斯表演变装秀
...stars in a drag show in Vegas.
我想和他交换生活圈
I think I want to trade circles.
相信我  你也不会想邀请他过来
Trust me. You don't want him there, either.
到时候没有人会看新娘...
Nobody will stare at the bride...
因为新郎的爸爸穿着露背连衣裙
...when the father of the groom is wearing a backless dress.
那又怎么样
So what?
只要他不穿婚纱  我根本不在乎
As long as he's not wearing a white dress and veil, I don't care.
我得去买点东西
I think I need to do some shopping.
太棒了
Nice.
我的天啊
My God!
你想要干什么
What do you think you're doing?
我只是在洗挡风玻璃
Just washing the windshield.
我绝不会让你开这辆车
There's no way I'm letting you drive this car.
你为什么不把钥匙还给我
Why don't you just hand over the keys.
别启动引擎
Do not start this car.
好吧  我给你二十块...
Okay, okay. I will give you 20 bucks...
只要你立刻下车  嘿
...if you get out of this car right now. Hey!
听着
Look.
如果你真的那么害怕  就快上车吧
Ross, if you're so freaked out, just get in the car.
跟你一起去兜风  好主意啊
With you? Yeah, right.
好吧
All right.
好吧...
Okay, okay, okay.
你这是要干嘛  坐到前面来
What are you doing? Get in the front.
你要我坐死亡座椅
In the death seat?!
-嘿  大家好  -嘿  亲爱的
- Hey, guys. - Hi, sweetie.
-准备要走了吗  -走吧
- Ready to go? - Yeah, sure.
我的皮包在莫妮卡家  我马上回来
I left my purse at Monica's. I'll be back.
-等一下  -干嘛
- Wait a minute. - What?
我还在头晕
That one kept going.
你跟菲比在交往哈
So, you and Phoebe, huh?
-你们交往多久了  -一个多月
- How long have you been going out? - Over a month.
我们应该多了解一下彼此
Maybe we ought to get to know each other a little better.
-好  我很乐意  -好  所以...
- Sure. I'd like that. - Yeah. So, uh...
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
-我是杰克  -我是乔伊
- It's Jake. - Joey.
你喜欢尼克队吗
Jake, do you like the Knicks?
当然  铁杆球迷
Yeah, big fan.
我也是  星期二有比赛你要一起去吗
Me too. There's a game on Tuesday. Do you want to go?
太棒了  我得先确定星期二没事
That'd be great! Let me make sure I'm not doing anything Tuesday.
拿去吧
Here.
-这是什么  -你的行李
- What's this? - It's your suitcase.
我们要去拉斯维加斯
We're going to Las Vegas.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
我们要私奔  不必再筹备那场愚蠢的婚礼了
You mean like eloping? No more stupid wedding stuff.
不必再烦恼要选哪种花
No more these flowers, these flowers, these flowers.
想想我们能省多少钱
Think of the money we'll save.
-我们不是要私奔  -我喜欢那些花
- We're not eloping. - I love the flowers.
我们的婚礼能办得再盛大一点吗  拜托
Can our wedding be bigger, please?
我们要去拉斯维加斯找你爸
We're going to Las Vagas to see your dad.
你们俩该谈谈了  我想认识我公公
It's time you two talked, and I want to get to know my father-in-law.
我们已经谈过这件事了  我赢了
We already went over this and I won.
不  你没赢  亲爱的  你应该知道
No, you didn't. Honey, just so you know...
你马上要娶我进门了  你以后就别想赢了
Now that you're marrying me, you don't get to win anymore.
算了吧  我不想去
Forget it, okay? I don't want to go.
我不想见到他  不想
I don't want to see him. I don't wanna.
我知道你爸让你觉得丢脸
Chandler, I know your dad embarrassed you. I know...
所有的孩子都会觉得自己的父母很丢脸
No, no, no. All kids are embarrassed by their parents.
你得想个新说法来形容我的苦痛经历
You'd have to come up with a new word for what I went through.
在高中的时候  他参加了我所有的游泳比赛
In high school, he used to come to all my swim meets...
每次都打扮成不一样的好莱坞明星
...dressed as a different Hollywood starlet.
我十四岁的日子很不好过
It's hard enough to be 14.
我瘦巴巴的  泳裤太大
You're skinny, you're wearing Speedos
我妈还说有一天我穿着会合身
that your mom promised you'd grow into.
我抬头看着看台  发现我爸在我为加油
You look up in the stands. There's your dad cheering you on.
他打扮成卡曼·米兰达
Dressed as Carmen Miranda,
戴着有真水果头饰的帽子
wearing a headdress with real fruit...
之后他会把那些水果分给你的朋友
...that he will later hand out to your friends
作为餐后水果
as a healthy snack.
重点是他参加了你每一场游泳比赛
The point is, he was at every one of your swim meets,
到现场帮你加油
and he was there cheering you on.
他是个好爸爸
That's a pretty great dad.
他跟嘉利巴迪先生上床了
He had sex with Mr. Garibaldi.
-谁是嘉利巴迪先生  -那很重要吗
- Who's Mr. Garibaldi? - Does it matter?!
你不再是十四岁的孩子  好吗
Chandler, you're not 14 anymore, okay?
你该忘了那些往事
Maybe it's time you let that stuff go.
如果他没来参加你的婚礼
If your father is not at your wedding,
你会遗憾终生的
you'll regret it for the rest of your life.
好吧  但我这么做是为了你
Okay, but I'm just doing this for you.
太棒了
Yes!
我永远都赢不了吗
So I never get to win anymore?
你以前又赢过几次
How much did you ever win before?
你知道当你穿着裤子
Listen, you know how when you're wearing pants
身体往前倾时  我可以看到你的内裤吗
and you lean forward, I check out your underwear?
知道
Yeah.
杰克弯腰的时候
Well, when Jake did it...
我看到他穿着女人的内裤
...I saw that he was wearing women's underwear.
我知道  那是我的内裤
I know. They were mine.
等一下  那样太奇怪了
No, no, wait. That's weird.
我们只是闹着玩
No, it's not. We were goofing around,
我跟他打赌他不敢穿
and I dared him to try them on.
那真的很奇怪
That's weird!
-我正穿着他的内裤  -那还挺性感的
- I'm wearing his briefs right now. - That's kind of hot.
我也这么觉得  你知道前面那个小洞吗
I think so too. And that little flap?
刚好可以拿来放我的口红
It's great for holding my lipstick.
这种事情我倒没机会知道
I wouldn't know about that.
杰克说  女人的内裤更舒服
Jake says that womers underwear is actually more comfortable.
他喜欢丝质内裤贴在皮肤上的感觉
And he loves how silk feels against his skin.
接下来他会说
Next thing you know, he'll be telling you
穿上你的高跟鞋他更婀娜多姿
that your high heels are good for his posture!
杰克没什么不正常的
There's nothing wrong with Jake.
他是个货真价实的男人
He is all man.
我担心的是你
I'm thinking even more than you.
他看起来像是穿着粉红色蕾丝内裤的伐木工人
He looked like a real lumberjack in those pink lacies.
我是说只有真正相信自己有男子气概的男人
I'm just saying only a man completely secure with his masculinity
才会穿上女人的内裤
could wear women's underwear.
我敢说你办不到
I don't think you could ever do that.
-我很相信自己的男子气概  -随便你
- I am secure with my masculinity. - Okay, whatever.
你看过我收集的色情杂志吧
You've seen my huge stack of porn, right?
天啊  我都忘了我有多爱开车
God, I forgot how much I love driving.
我得去换新驾照
I have got to get my license renewed.
你的驾照过期了
You don't have a valid driver's license?
好了  马上停车
Okay, that's it. Pull over right now.
罗斯  你太紧张了
Ross, you're so tense.
你得放轻松  好吗
You just gotta relax, okay?
你只需要放轻松  好吗  放轻松
Just need to relax. All right? Just need to relax.
你再...  那一点都不好笑  别闹了
What are you...? That's not funny. Stop horsing around.
我没有胡闹  好吗
I am not horsing around, okay?
我在"开保时捷"兜风
I am "Porsche-ing" around.
保持冷静  不会有事的
Stay calm. Nothing is gonna happen to you.
你没有惹上大麻烦
You're not in that much trouble.
真的吗  你那么觉得
Really? You think so?
我是在跟自己说话  你死定了
I was talking to myself. You're going down!
有人来帮你们点东西了吗
Has someone taken your order yet?
对  她来过了  是他才对  是她吗
Oh, yeah. She did. He did. She?
抱歉  我第一次来  我不...
I'm sorry, I'm new. I don't...
我点了一杯啤酒
I just ordered a beer.
你是异性恋  我懂了
You're straight. I get it.
如果我们打电话给你爸
I still say that if we called your dad,
就能占到比较好一点的位置
we could've gotten better seats.
我不想让他知道我们来了
No, no. I don't want him to know we're here yet.
我还没有准备好
I'm not sure I'm ready for that.
而且他看到我也不会太高兴
Besides, he won't be too happy to see me either.
为什么
Why not?
我不知道我有没有告诉你...
I don't know if I told you this,
过去几年他常常试着跟我联络
but he's kind of tried to contact me a lot over the last few years.
什么
What?
对  他会打电话  写信给我
Yeah. He's made phone calls, written letters.
他会到纽约来  但我总是说我很忙
He came to New York. But I always said I was too busy to see him.
就像是"恶意缺席"  我真的不想谈
It's very "Cats in the Cradle." I don't want to get into it.
节日要开始了
Here we go.
各位先生女士  欢迎与世无双的...
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome the incomparable...
海莲娜·汉德巴斯奇
...Helena Handbasket.
嗨  我的小亲亲们
Hello, darlings.
他就是我爸
And there's Daddy.
快跟我换位置
Switch places with me. Switch places with me.
快点  我在上面  你在下面
Come on! I'll go under, you go over.
-对  我愿意那么做  -快点  罗斯
- Yeah, I'll get right on that. - Come on, Ross!
-什么  别  瑞秋  别那样  -快点
- What? No. Hey, Rach, come on. - Come on!
我相信我们不会因此被逮捅
I'm sure we won't get arrested for this.
天啊
God!
嗨  警官  我的速度有点快吗
Hi, officer. Was I going a little too fast?
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
-麻烦你把驾照拿出来  -没问题
- Can I see your license, please? - Yes, absolutely.
这太奇怪了  我昨晚做了一个梦
It's weird. I had a dream last night
梦到我被一个警察拦下来
that I was stopped by a policeman.
然后他...
And then he...
或许我不该告诉你接下来的情节
Well, I probably shouldn't tell you the rest.
你的驾照
Your license.
对  在这里  警官...
Yes. Here you go, Officer...
帅哥警官
...Handsome.
-是韩森才对  -对不起  我看错了
- It's Hanson. - Oops, sorry. My mistake.
我的天啊
Dear Lord!
-哇  -准备受死吧
- Wow! - Here it comes.
这张照片很漂亮
This is a great picture.
真的吗  你真那么想
Really? You think so?
拍照时我才刚刚起床
You know, I had just rolled right out of bed.
你看起来很美
You look phenomenal.
能不美吗  那是十年前的照片了
She should! It was taken 10 years ago!
你知道的  你可能会纳闷日期有点不太对劲
You know, you're probably wondering about the old date.
没错  你是水瓶座吗
Yes, I am. You're an Aquarius, huh?
-我敢说你是双子座  -不是
- I'll bet you're a Gemini. - No.
-金牛座  -不是
- Taurus? - No.
-处女座  -不是
- Virgo? - No.
-射手座  -对
- Sagittarius? - Yep.
我就知道
I knew it. I knew it!
-不要再超速了  好吗  -我不会超速的
- I'll tell what? You won't speed anymore, right? - I won't speed.
你发誓你会去换驾照
And you promise you'll get this taken care of right away?
-我发誓  -还有  最好让他开车
- I promise. - In the meantime, you better let him drive.
-他有驾照吗  -有
- Does he have a license? - Yeah.
-他会开手动档的车吗  -那个
- Can he handle a stick? - Well...
我会开手动的车
I can handle a stick!
我感觉很美
I feel pretty.
非常美
Oh so pretty.
-我感觉自己美丽  智慧  -是同性恋
- I feel pretty and witty and... - Gay!
他不可能是你爸
That can't be your father.
多年来我一直是那么告诉自己
Believe me. I've been saying that for years.
-我的天啊  -怎么了
- Oh, my God! - What?
弹钢琴的人就是嘉利巴迪先生
That's Mr. Garibaldi playing the piano.
因为我被帅气出色的小伙所爱
For I'm loved by a pretty wonderful boy!
嗨  欢迎你们来看表演
Hello, and welcome to the show.
在观众席中我看到一些常客
I see some of our regulars in the audience.
还有一些新面孔
And a couple of irregulars.
他要走进观众席里了  他要走进观众席里了
He's coming into the audience. He's coming into the audience.
放轻松  你会没事的
Relax. You'll be fine.
好多了  现在你成了隐形人
Oh, much better. You're invisible now.
-你是从哪里来的  -贝克斯菲德
- Where are you from? - Bakersfield.
-对不起  -贝克斯菲德
- I'm sorry? - Bakersfield.
不  我听到了  我只是觉得很遗憾
No, no, I heard. I'm just sorry.
我无法面对这种事情  我们回酒店碰面
It can't happen like this. I'll meet you back at the hotel.
大家看  已经有人站起来鼓掌
Look, a standing ovation already.
节目才刚刚开始
So early in the show.
转身吧  亲爱的  让我看看你帅气的脸
Turn around, darling. Let me see your pretty face.
我们的饮料能快点送上来吗
Can we have our drinks, please?
服务生  小姐
Waiter? ...tress?
-嘿  菲比  -嘿
- Hey, Pheebs. - Hey.
你看
Check it out.
我很有男子气概吧
How much of a man am I?
哇  太棒了
Wow, nice.
你很有男子气概  还有点淫荡
Manly, and also kind of a slut.
我开始明白杰克的意思了
You know. I'm beginning to see what Jake was talking about.
丝质内裤感觉真的很舒服
The silk feels really good.
而那玩意不像我想象中会挤成一团
And things aren't as smashed down as I thought they would be.
那真的是太棒了  乔伊
That's great, Joe.
男人的内裤选择就没那么多了
You have so many more choices than with men's underwear.
比基尼  法式剪栽  丁字裤
Bikini, French cut, thong.
质料有棉  丝  蕾丝
And the fabrics: you got cotton, silk, lace.
你知道我一直想穿什么吗  裤袜
You know what I've always wondered about? Pantyhose!
从脚趾头开始一路住上拉到...
The way they start at your toe, then they go all the way up to...
我应该把内裤脱下来了  对吧
I should go take these off, shouldn't I ?
你最好脱了吧
I think it's important you do.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
钱德勒
Chandler.
Chandler?
那个名字真是与众不同
What an unusual name.
你的父母一定很出色
You must have had terribly fascinating parents.
他们很有幽默感
Oh, they're a hoot.
你的朋友叫什么名字
And who is your friend?
我是莫妮卡
I'm Monica.
-莫妮卡  你们从哪里来的  -纽约
- Monica. Where are you from? - New York.
我不太喜欢纽约
I'm not very fond of New York.
但我喜欢皇后区[变装皇后]
Queens, I like.
这个亮晶晶的...
What is this...
东西是什么  亲爱的
...sparkling something, honey, huh?
事实上莫妮卡跟我订婚了
Actually, Monica and I are engaged.
真的吗
Really?
恭喜你们
Congratulations.
你们什么时候结婚
When's the big day?
两星期后
In two weeks.
我知道了
I see.
我祝你们两个永远幸福
Well, I wish you both a lifetime of happiness.
原来你是个秃头
So, you're bald.
等一下
Wait, wait.
我们希望你能来参加我们的婚礼
We'd love it if you could be there.
真的吗
Really?
你能来我会觉得很开心
I know it would make me happy...
夫人
...ma'am.
我一定会去的
Then I wouldn't miss it for the world.
我都热泪盈眶了
I'm getting all misty here.
你们一定会以为我刚刚用热蜡除过腿毛
You'd think I was having my legs waxed or something.
-你还好吗  -我很好
- You okay? - Yeah.
谢谢你逼我这么做
Thanks for making me do this.
在继续表演前
Before we go on with the show,
我要跟这对新人说...
I want to say to the bride and groom...
他们非常幸运能邂逅彼此
...how lucky they are to have found each other.
每个人的人生都会遇到雨天
In every life a little rain must fall.
还好...
Fortunately...
在我的人生中...
...in my life...
-天上在下男人  -哈利路亚
- It's raining men! - Hallelujah!
-天上在下男人  -阿门
- It's raining men! - Amen!
我小时候演过最左边那个角色
When I was growing up, I played the one on the far left.
提醒我介绍你给某人认识
Remind me to introduce you to someone.
-谁  -四档
- Who? - Fourth gear.
他想做什么  我什么都没做
What does he want? I wasn't doing anything.
或许他看到你的手
Maybe he saw your hands
只会从十点的位置滑到两点的位置
slip briefly from the 10 and 2:00 position.
或许是射手座警官折回来想泡你
Maybe it's Sergeant Sagittarius coming back to flirt some more.
不是刚刚那个警官
It's a different guy.
晚上好  警官
Good evening, officer.
你知道你的时速有多快吗
Do you know how fast you were travelling back there?
我不知道  但应该没有超过六十英里
No, I don't, but it couldn't have been more than 60.
你说得对  只有三十七英里
You're right. It was 37.
你该不会因为我开得太慢而开我罚单吧
You're not gonna give me a ticket for driving too slow, are you?
没错
That's right.
你知道的  警官...
You know, officer...
昨晚我做了一个非常奇怪的梦
I had the weirdest dream last night.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
麻烦你把驾照拿出来
Your license, please.
你不想想听听我做了什么梦...
You don't want to hear about my dream...
警官...
...Officer...
...可爱警官
...Pretty?
是佩坦警官才对
It's Petty.
我马上帮你开罚单
I'll be right back with your ticket.
-你有个儿子  -我知道
- You have a son. - I know. I know.
-你觉得好一点了吗  -我好多了
- You feel better? - Yeah. Much.
听着...
Listen...
我并不是担心我的男子气概...
Not that I'm insecure about my manood or anything...
但我觉得我应该马上去泡个女人
...but I think I need to hook up with a woman right now.
我了解
I understand.
你看起来好眼熟  我认识你吗
You look familiar. Do I know you from somewhere?
应该不认识
I don't think so.
或许因为我是电视演员
Maybe it's because I'm on television.
-我演过《我们的日子》  -真的吗
- I'm an actor on Days of our Lives. - Wow. Really?
-一共是四块半  谢谢  -让我来吧
- $4.50, please. - Oh, let me get this.
这是送你的
These are for you.